was/were and could
Gordon was Jeremy’s business partner.
They were at his country house.
They could hear a strange noise.
She wasn’t at home last night.
You weren’t very nice to her.
I couldn’t sleep.
Were you sick yesterday? When was he born?
Could you see anybody in the library?
regular verbs
I really liked the present. She wanted to be a doctor.
She didn’t enjoy the concert. They didn’t arrive until very late.
Did you watch the game last night? When did you finish the book?
irregular verbs
I went to Paris last summer. She slept on the sofa.
He didn’t come home last night. They didn’t hear the music.
Did you speak to your sister yesterday? Where did you have lunch?